



Hello, I have more than 7 years of experience in the field of Web Designing. I've been doing website development and management in my last workplace. I have experience in building and managing corporate websites (based wordpress cms and HTML/CSS) for the company, where I worked and for clients. In addition to this, I have experience building cloud file sharing systems (using systems like nextcloud, owncloud). I have experience building small web tools (such as corporate mail signature and corporate ID card creation tools).



## **CONTACT ME**



+998 93 630 2069



info@nematullo.com



### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

WordPress

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

Adobe Photoshop



#### **GET IN TOUCH**



NEMATULLO.COM



LINKEDIN.COM/IN/NEMATULLO



#### WORK EXPERIENCE

SZUTEST Technology

Web Developer in Istanbul, TR September 2017 - 2022

Web Design/Development Search Engine Optimization (SEO)

SZUTEST

Graphic & Web Designer in Istanbul, TR October 2016 - 2022

Web Design Graphic Design

FREELANCER

Freelance Web Developer 2013 - 2016



#### **EDUCATION** \*=

ANDIJAN COMPUTER TECHNOLOGY COLLEGE (2010-2013)

Specialist in Information and Communication Systems ICT Specialist directed on Business

STUDY CENTER AT THE ANDIJAN STATE UNIVERSITY (2010-2012)

English Language

English Teacher and Translator

# Q COURSES / CERTIFICATES

HTML CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2017

CSS CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2018

JAVASCRIPT CERTIFICATE

SoloLearn 2020

TECHNICAL SEO CERTIFICATE

SEMrush 2021

THE ONLINE MARKETING FUNDAMENTALS

Google 2017



## LANGUAGES \_\_\_\_\_

ENGLISH

RUSSIAN

TURKISH

**UZBEK**